I CAN SING A BILLION SONGS
DANCE TILL MY FEET ARE NUMB
SPIN TILL I'M EMPTY AND POOR
I CAN'T PRAISE YOU ENOUGH
I CAN SHOUT TILL MY VOICE GIVES WAY
LEAP TILL I HAVE NO STRENGTH
LOSE MY BREATH TRYING TO EXPLAIN
I CAN'T PRAISE YOU ENOUGH
AND IF TIME WERE TO STALL
I CAN NEVER TELL IT ALL
WORDS ARE FEW
THIS WILL HAVE TO DO
I JUST WANNA THANK YOU
I'M SO GRATEFUL
YOU SANG TILL I FOUND MY SONG
YOU DANCED TILL MY HEART WOKE UP
NOW I MOVE TO THE RHYTHM OF LOVE
I CAN'T PRAISE YOU ENOUGH
YOU WEPT TILL I FOUND MY STRENGTH
YOU LOST YOUR BREATH DYING TO SAVE ME
I'LL NEVER GO BACK TO THAT GRAVE
I CAN'T PRAISE YOU ENOUGH
AND IF TIME WERE TO STALL
I CAN NEVER TELL IT ALL
WORDS ARE FEW
THIS WILL HAVE TO DO
I JUST WANNA THANK YOU
I'M SO GRATEFUL
ALL MY STRENGTH IS FOUND IN YOU
ALL MY JOY IS FOUND IN YOUR LORD
I'M STANDING IN YOUR PROMISE
SURROUNDED BY YOUR GOODNESS
YOU HAVE OVERWHELMED US
HALLELUJAH
I'M STANDING IN YOUR PROMISE
SURROUNDED BY YOUR GOODNESS
YOU HAVE OVERWHELMED US
HALLELUJAH
AND IF TIME WERE TO STALL
I CAN NEVER TELL IT ALL
WORDS ARE FEW
THIS WILL HAVE TO DO
AND IF TIME WERE TO STALL
I CAN NEVER TELL IT ALL
WORDS ARE FEW
THIS WILL HAVE TO DO
I JUST WANNA THANK YOU
I'M SO GRATEFUL